Corruption discovered
at the core of the Banking Clan!
Reunited, Rush Clovis
and Senator Amidala
discover the full extent
of the deception.
Anakin Skywalker is sent to the rescue!
He refuses to trust Clovis and
asks Padm not to work with him.
Determined to save the banks,
she refuses her husband's request,
throwing their
relationship into turmoil.
Voted for by both the
Separatists and the Republic,
Rush Clovis is elected new leader
of the Galactic Banking Clan.
Now, all attention is focused on Scipio
as the important
transfer of power begins.
Welcome back to Scipio, Rush Clovis.
Our Separatist government
has great hopes for you.
Thank you, Senator.
Only you and Senator Amidala
will be allowed to monitor
the exchange proceedings.
No forces on either side
will be allowed
into the Neutral Zone.
Senator Amidala,
we will be right here
if you should need us.
Thank you, Commander.
It is with great disappointment
that I implement
the following verdict.
By decree of the Muun people,
the five representatives
standing before me
are found guilty
of embezzlement.
They shall be imprisoned
forthwith,
and control of the banks
shall transfer immediately
to Rush Clovis
under the guidance
of the Muun government.
We are grateful to you, Clovis,
for everything you have done
for the Muun people.
To have lost the banks
would have been
an historic disaster.
I would like you to know
I have no interest
in controlling the banks.
I am simply here
to reestablish order.
Do you think our friend
is up to the task?
There are few men
I have met in my career
who are more dedicated
to a cause than Clovis.
Once he decides
what he is fighting for,
little will stop him
from achieving it.
Let us hope you are right
for all our sakes.
Ah, Clovis.
How are you liking
your new office?
I must say, you look very
comfortable behind that desk.
Count Dooku,
what do I owe the pleasure?
Come, come, my boy.
You don't think I'd let
such an important day pass
without wishing you
the best of luck.
Thank you, but luck
has nothing to do with it.
The transfer has occurred
without a hitch.
Well, of course it has.
The Separatists are fully
behind your appointment.
After all, aren't we the ones
who put you there?
For your support, I am grateful,
but I now must lead
without allegiance
towards either side.
Is that so?
Quite the idealist you have become
in so short a time.
What do you want, Dooku?
To collect on my investment.
How do you think the Republic
would like to know
that it was I
who supplied Rush Clovis
with all the information
he needed
to topple the leaders of the bank?
I will tell them myself.
Oh, but you can't.
I put you in power.
You belong to me,
and if you want to stay in control,
you will do as I say.
The banks will remain unbiased.
Then I'm afraid the Separatists
will be unable to pay
the interest on our loans.
But the banks will collapse,
and then...
Not if you raise
interest rates on the Republic.
What?
You know I can't do that.
Oh, but you can, and you will,
or everything that you
fought so hard for
will be destroyed.
By the new order
of the Traxus Division
and in an attempt
to stabilize the banks,
it is essential that interest
rates on loans to the Republic
be raised immediately.
What?
But you can't do that!
Clovis.
Clovis!
What are you doing?
This is an outrage!
We warned you this would happen!
And what of the Separatists?
From the little information.
Senator Amidala
has been able to establish,
there will be no raise
on their current loan.
I knew from the beginning
that Clovis would do this.
Hmm, correct you might have been
about Clovis.
It's incredibly foolish
for to make a move like this
so early.
He will turn the whole Republic
against him.
Not clear to us
are his objectives.
Want this he might.
Something's wrong.
This doesn't make sense.
I would like
to call for restraint
and allow us time
to analyze the situation.
You may begin your attack.
It is time to make Rush Clovis
look like a powerful Separatist.
Right away, sir.
It looks like
an invasion fleet, sir.
We're caught out here
in the open.
Get the men off this landing pad
and beyond the city gates!
Senator Amidala,
come in, please.
What is it, Commander Thorn?
We're under attack
by the Separatist garrison.
Looks to be a full invasion.
Invasion?
We can't get to you.
I suggest you get to a ship
as soon as you can.
Boom!
Ahh!
Let's move!
Hurry!
Ah!
For the Republic!
Our garrison has been attacked
by the Separatists,
and it appears they are staging
an invasion of Scipio.
An invasion?
What do they hope to achieve?
With this news, the Senate
will vote immediately
to attack Scipio.
It appears war has already
come to Scipio.
I want you off that planet
immediately.
I can't.
Surely you can get to a ship.
General Skywalker,
I'm afraid I'm trapped.
Let me go!
Invoke an emergency meeting
of the Senate.
There is no time to lose.
I feel it is only right
that you should handle
this matter, my boy.
A lot will be entrusted to you.
Don't touch me!
What have you done to her?
Clovis, what is going on?
I didn't want this, Padm.
Why don't you tell her
what you did want
and how you got it.
Dooku.
Padm, this is not what it seems.
Hasn't she joined our cause?
Clovis here told me
how instrumental you were
in getting him to power.
If I had known...
Either you are with us
or you are against us.
Arrest her!
We can't do this, Dooku.
The Separatist Senate
will never approve.
Hey!
No. No.
No!
Are you insane?
This was not part of the deal.
What deal?
What have you done here, Clovis?
He's given us the banks.
Gone are our debts,
and gone is any credit
for the Republic.
All of your idealism
was just a front.
There was nothing I could do.
Everyone has their price,
my dear.
It is with grave news
I come before you.
Count Dooku and his
Separatist betrayers
have manipulated us, my friends.
The war must go to Scipio!
Clovis has been
their puppet of deceit
as the Separatists are
currently invading Scipio.
We must stop them
and secure the planet!
We have handed
the entire economic system
over to Count Dooku.
We are doomed!
Invade!
As Supreme Chancellor,
I must abide
by the consensus of the Senate.
We shall commence
a mercy mission to Scipio
to be led by
General Anakin Skywalker.
The banks will be secured
at all costs,
and the Republic
will not crumble!
Victory!
We will take victory.
War on Scipio!
Great emotions
you will find on Scipio,
will you not?
I am worried
for Senator Amidala.
I'm afraid we may be too late.
Correct you were about Clovis,
but let go of your selfishness
you must
if you are to see clearly.
Not all is as it seems.
I understand, Master.
Lord Tyranus, the Republic fleet
will be arriving shortly.
Very good, my lord.
Clovis has blindly
played his part.
It now appears he coordinated
the entire Separatist takeover.
And because of this treachery,
the banks will be firmly placed
under the control
of the Supreme Chancellor.
Why are you doing this?
You wouldn't understand.
I had to strike a deal
with Dooku,
but don't worry.
I am the one in control.
As soon as things
have settled down,
I can get rid of him,
and I'll control it all again.
Listen to yourself.
The Republic is sending
its armada
to take back the banks.
You've brought war
right where there cannot be war.
Your actions
have destroyed the banks
once and for all!
Rex, have you gotten a fix
on Senator Amidala's position?
We'll have a better lock
once we get near the city,
but initial scans suggest
she's still alive, sir.
Good.
Hawk, we're gonna need
air support
once we're on the ground.
You'll have it, General.
Me and the boys
are ready to fly.
My Lord,
we have fully engaged
Republic forces,
but we are suffering
heavy losses.
We have accomplished
what we came here for.
It is time to withdraw.
But sir, our forces
are still engaged
in battle on the planet.
Leave them.
As you wish, Count Dooku.
Sir, a Republic attack fleet
has just entered orbit
and is approaching the city.
Get me Count Dooku.
It appears Count Dooku
has left the planet's surface.
What?
And the Separatist forces
are in full retreat.
We are alone.
Rex, hold the droid forces here.
I'm gonna push on and get Padm.
Copy that.
Such plans I had.
You know, I've spent so much
of my life misunderstood.
What will they say about me now?
What will I have left behind?
Clovis, you have to
turn yourself in.
It's over, Clovis.
Stay away from me!
I didn't do anything wrong!
You have to believe me!
You don't want to do this.
You don't understand.
You've all been deceived.
Yeah, by you.
No!
By Dooku.
I'm not the villain here.
Tell him, Padm.
Let me go, Clovis.
I can't hold both of you.
Let me go.
No, Anakin, don't.
Try and climb.
I am!
I'm losing you!
I'm sorry, Padm.
No.
It's okay.
You're okay.
I'm sorry, Anakin.
I'm sorry.
It's over now.
It's all over now.
It is clear to the Banking Clan
it was Rush Clovis who was
behind the corruption
that almost caused our collapse.
In hope of a better tomorrow,
we cede control of the banks
to the office of the Chancellor
of the Galactic Republic.
It is with great humility
that I take on
this immense responsibility.
Rest assured,
when the Clone Wars end,
I shall reinstate the banks
as we once knew them,
but during these
treacherous times,
we cannot in good conscience
allow our money
to fall under the manipulations
of a madman like Count Dooku
or Separatist control again.
May there be prosperity
and stability
in all our Republic lands.
May our people be free and safe.
Long live the banks!